Contact

faisal.m13574@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/md-faisal-878628202 (LinkedIn) faisal413.github.io/profile.com/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Html

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
JavaScript

Md Faisal

Data Entry Operator at Income Tax Department Of UK Comilla District

Summary

I am Faisal. And I am game Developer. Experienced Data Entry Operator with a demonstrated history of working in the government administration industry. Skilled in Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Office, Microsoft Access, Microsoft PowerPoint, C (Programming Language), HTML(Hyper Text Markup Language), CSS (Cascading Style Sheets) ,JavaScript and Unity (game engine).

Experience

Unity Technologies

Game Developer

December 2020 - Present (3 months)

Income Tax Department Of UK
Data Entry Operator
March 2020 - Present (1 year)
UK

Education

Adarsha Pre-Cadet School SSC · (2020 - 2022)